findnearyou.com 2008-06-11

# FindNearYou.com :: Privacy Policy

Privacy matters are accorded high priority at [ www.findnearyou.com](http://www.findnearyou.com/) (FNY). Please read on to know more about our privacy policy

The privacy policy covers the way FNY uses personal information collected when you registers and subsequently log onto the site and when you use FNY’s services. This policy however does not apply to the practices of companies not connected with FNY or to persons not associated with FNY.

Upon registration when you first visit FNY, an automatic link will be sent to your email address which when clicked will activate your account with FNY. Since then, you can log onto FNY with your email id and password. FNY will communicate with you over this email id provided.

Registered users have the liberty to add more personal information on Mylist Page and this information will be kept confidential by FNY.

FNY will never sell/rent/lease out your personal information unless instructed by you. The personal information collected from you will be used by FNY, its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized, and may also be used to request additional information on feedback that you provide about the product or service that you are using; to provide notifications regarding new services; to improve the our service, or to provide you with advance notice of events and loyalty rewards and offers.The URL of the website from which you visit FNY, the IP address of your computer and ISP and other attributes like browser software, date of your visit etc. are transmitted in line with the communication standards of the internet industry and these are logged by FNY for study. 

FNY will be in touch with you thru regular Newsletters containing tips on various topics You can make changes to your personal information at any time by logging into FNY. In the event of you wanting to disassociate with FNY, a written communication needs to be sent to [ feedback@findnearyou.com](mailto:feedback@findnearyou.com) and we will take necessary steps to close your account. 

You hereby acknowledge that personal information is being provided voluntarily. 

FNY may disclose personal information about the user if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on FNY or one of its Web sites, (b) protect and defend the rights or property of FNY and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of FNY employees, users of FNY services, or members of the public.
